<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">CitySweep</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_single_player">SinglePlayer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_multi">Multi</string>
    <string name="title_activity_host__bt">host_BT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_start_screen">startScreen</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="title_activity_device_list">DeviceListActivity</string>


    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="not_connected">You are not connected to a device</string>
    <string name="bt_not_enabled_leaving">Bluetooth was not enabled. Leaving Bluetooth Chat.</string>
    <string name="title_connecting">connecting...</string>
    <string name="title_connected_to">connected: </string>
    <string name="title_not_connected">not connected</string>

    <!--  DeviceListActivity -->
    <string name="scanning">scanning for devices...</string>
    <string name="select_device">select a device to connect</string>
    <string name="none_paired">No devices have been paired</string>
    <string name="none_found">No devices found</string>
    <string name="title_paired_devices">Paired Devices</string>
    <string name="title_other_devices">Other Available Devices</string>
    <string name="button_scan">Scan for devices</string>
    <string name="details">\ \ \ \ \ \ \ \ \ \ \     Cleanliness is next to Godliness. Its our duty to make our city clean and beautiful and that is the objective of this game.
its a game of your memory and reasoning.\n
\n
GOAL: Find the empty square,avoid the garbage and keep the city clean. The faster you clean the city the better you score.
\n\n
HOW TO PLAY:
\n\n
Rules are simple-
\n
Single player:\n
->Uncover the garbage ,the game ends.\n\n
->Uncover an empty square, and you keep cleaning(playing).\n\n
->Uncover a number, and it tells you how much garbage lay hidden in the eight surrounding squares—information you use to
 deduce which nearby squares are safe to click.\n\n
\n
Multiplayer:\n\n
Whosoever will complete the cleaning first will be the winner.\n

Sounds easy, Right?\n
Lets make it easier,\n

To make your cleaning faster and easier you will be provided with 4 lifelines which are hidden inside the squares.
You can use these lifelines whenever you want to. these are:\n\n
1.  Insta Clean: This lifeline will save you from losing if there is garbage hidden inside the square you have clicked
               just after activating this lifeline. basically it will clean that garbage.\n
2.  Down the Drain: Through this lifeline you can make your opponent fall into the sewage hole and he/she will remain there
               for 8 sec i.e., he/she cannot click on any of the squares in these 8 seconds.\n
3.  Armor: This lifeline will be activated for 15 seconds.In these 15 sec if your opponent uses \'down the drain\' lifeline
           then armor will protect you.\n
4.  Garbage Displacement: the most interesting one. you can displace the garbage of your opponent to ny place you want. just
             you have to think before you take the action.\n
\n
Hints and tips:\n\n

>Mark the garbage : If you suspect a square conceals a garbage, right-click it. This puts a broom on the square.\n
\n
>Study the patterns. If three squares in a row display 2-3-2, then you know three garbage are probably lined up
                    beside that row.If a square says 8, every surrounding square has a garbage beside it.\n
\n
Explore the unexplored. Not sure where to click next? Try clearing some unexplored territory. You\'re better off
                     clicking in the middle of unmarked squares than in an area you suspect contains garbage.\n
\n
ALL THE BEST! :D\n</string>


</resources>
